<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Evan Merlock - Official Website</title>
    <link>https://evan.merlock.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Evan Merlock - Official Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 23:23:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://evan.merlock.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Constructum</title>
      <link>https://evan.merlock.dev/projects/constructum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 23:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evan.merlock.dev/projects/constructum/</guid>
      <description>Constructum Constructum is a custom-built CI/CD pipeline for my homelab.
It runs on top of Kubernetes, given that my homelab is based around my Kubernetes cluster.
Features  Runs simple pipelines defined in internal Git repositories Has secret support to derive secrets from various secret stores  Upcoming Features  A user interface for easy access to logs / details A command-line tool for running pipelines locally and communicating with the API server Integration with the source-control tool I use Multiple pipelines per repository  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Website</title>
      <link>https://evan.merlock.dev/posts/init/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 23:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evan.merlock.dev/posts/init/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my new website! Will I write blog posts? Will I ever update it after this first time? We&amp;rsquo;ll find out together&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theta</title>
      <link>https://evan.merlock.dev/projects/theta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 23:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evan.merlock.dev/projects/theta/</guid>
      <description>Theta Theta is my toy programming language, with roots coming from Lox of Crafting Interpreters fame, Java, and Rust. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to be a starting place for further exploration of programming language concepts I didn&amp;rsquo;t learn in college.
This project took a back-seat due to the need for a competent CI/CD pipeline &amp;ndash; see Constructum.
Features  Bytecode compiler and interpreter for basic expressions Support for statements Block support Static typing  Upcoming Features  Stack frames Function support Structure / Object support Interface or traits?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
